Synchronized across all the different
environments, all the all the data. So we
can do some testing for the products that
have that dependency on on the detectors.
OK, so we don't need to do everything, we
just need to do the detectors.
If that can be done, yes.
We also testing e-mail, so we don't
have emailing Deb. So anything that
instead of 2 emails, I think also
that that's also the detectors, right? So
actually let me think about it. Let
me think about this. Yes, it's data
classes, the data classes. The initial
remote as well, because that's whether
you're not use. Yeah. So they're pushing
their classes. That's probably why we
would like to have done first, OK. And
then eventually we'll just move all the
rules. I mean, we don't need to move all
the rules and stuff over right now. We
just need to move the detectives and data
classes. And then when you guys are ready
to go into production, we'll move. Yeah,
we'll basically do like a refresh of all
of the data classes and detectors and
make sure they're all up to date and then
also do the rules.
Well, also keep in mind, right, that that
we have multiple environments, they're
current product, right? So at some point
we're going to have the authorization to
move to that, right? And we will probably
come and ask. You can now move everything
including rules and everything to that,
right? That will get us closer to where
we want to be. Then as soon as we get
into recession to move to. We will
probably ask you to move everything from
path to prod. OK, alright.
It just unfortunately it's just the the
way they like to do things internally,
right. They don't want us to move from
one environment to another without
getting their permission and analyzing
race and all that kind of stuff, which I
mean agreement with that.
Yeah, I actually, I saw your e-mail
this morning. So I reached out to
that resource and he he had sent
me or he said he's going to
send me those. There's one script for
e-mail, one for the ITM platform. I
guess we won't need the. Yeah.
OK. So yeah, we'll just move all of the.
Can you just send me an e-mail like the
like where stuff needs to go, like the
tenants, like it needs to go from. So I
know you guys have like a few different
ones and it's hard to kind of track all
of the names. So if you could just let me
know where it exists today and then where
it needs to go just to shoot me an e-mail
that it should be good. OK. Yeah,
we'll do, Joseph. Alright. Detectors will
need to go in all the different
environments that we have because
everything set up today, direct classes,
they probably need to go to the path. So
I'll let you know what that is.
I well, I mean the, the data classes will
probably even for endpoint will probably
just move them over, right? Because
otherwise you'll have all the detectors
there. But you'll, you'll then need to
create the data classes again. So we
might as well just move them all over.
That makes sense. OK, perfect. Yep. Yep,
it does. Ohh you
just show your picture OK?Ohh, did
that just change on zoom? Yeah, I changed
it this morning. I guess it just like did
a sync on Zoom now.
The IT was funny because I'm actually
switching the screens and the first thing
that I noticed that the picture just
changed in front of me. Like what? What
happened here? OK, OK.
All right, So yeah, I guess the scripts
from him today and then yeah, maybe at
next week we can get together. I don't
know if I'll necessarily need you guys
really on a call to do it. I should be
able to just do it in the back end, so.
Yeah, I'll keep you updated on that. But
I think Max, we can aim for next week.
Yeah, if it can be early next week,
that would be great, right. It's it's
just that we either we actually get you
guys through that or our guys just start
doing stuff manually so we can test some
stuff. Yeah. No, no, we can, we can
move it over for you. OK, perfect. I
guess is being. Few minutes since 11:00,
so we can probably get started, uh,
before we start, I do have few things
that I would like to go over with you
guys. Uh, I, and
this is probably for now, I don't think,
I don't know, I don't know, I haven't
seen that on this call, but I, I
was, I was asking about the ignition
diagram for that proposed solution for,
for the stories. You guys can implement a
new API that that reflected the pool. So
we're trying to. 25 They're stagnant that
we can actually take back to our
different teams and you know, have the
conversation and show them what what you
guys are proposing and how the flow is
going to look like, right?
I understand it was that the the the
there was going to be something.
In the last couple of days but I didn't
see anything so I was trying to get an
update on that. I, I
follow up this morning, so let's see if
you answered for that. Yeah, that's one
of the things that I would like to get
some feedback sooner than later.
The next thing in my in my list
will be the 80 integration um.
Just to I want to go over this specific
items with you, Ali. Sorry, Harry, just
to make sure I'm not missing anything
here. Alright, so let me just share my
screen. Just
because you know, Fernandez been away for
a while and I I want to make sure that I
know you guys haven't had this
conversation, but I also need to
understand how this is going to work. So
give me a second. I'm just going to pull
this up here.
But I don't want to look into that. I
want to look into that so.
The Council.
Ohh.
Hey Harris team, sorry I'm late, I was in
another meeting running long.
No worries, we already started, so don't
don't forget. I
I had your e-mail response drafted, uh,
for your couple of questions. I'm still
working on and chasing internally, but I
didn't mean to interrupt. Whatever it is
you're working on, I can wait until the
end or share brief updates as best as
possible. No worries. So yeah, let's
do it for a let me go over the list and
then we can get the update for you. I
just need to get some stuff from my my
list just for a piece of mine and then
we'll get there. Just because I sent
somebody an e-mail. So I don't know what
she was talking about, but yeah, I I sent
two of them. OK, Harris, can you see my
screen?Ohh, nothing to guess
my screen. No of course you guys get
out. You can actually share the that will
work. Getting the
prompt? OK, maybe this. There
we go. Sure.
OK. Yeah. Just to clarify,
so we're going to have
policies in that will require
that we integrate with Active
Directory and that we actually
have eighty groups synced to
this platform, right?
We are working on an integration,
sorry in apparation that's going to
allow us to have.
Should allow us to to come
up with the saying that that
is required. So just to make
sure that I understand what is
required I will need to come
into create any.
You would go cancel your go
to integration, yes, OK. And then
cloud apps. Clarifications
and then I will have
to select.
Yeah, the third one.
Ohh, there we go. And then I will
do identity, identity only, right? That's
what what was the what you guys
suggested? Yeah, that's right, but you
guys do. So let me ask you this,
you guys did also let me actually double
check, but you guys, I think you guys
did also buy the cloud. The P uh
yeah, you did. So you also bought Casby.
So at some point you're going to connect
this whole thing, right? So it's up to
you guys. If you want to just make the
connection now, then you'll get the AD
groups as well. Otherwise, when you set
up Cloud, you'll need to have a new
connector with the regular configuration.
Right. We can just update the permission
and the scope of the of the application,
right. OK, so I'm, I apologize, just bear
with me for a second. So we're going to
come, we're going to do this. We're not
we're going to go and retrieve only uses
related data. What exactly proof point is
following when, when this connection gets
made?A little bit like group.
I think it should be, ohh, it's not on
that document, right? So I think it's
group. Group membership, Rita, I'll
have to check the exact permission. So I
think it's only like 4 or three or four
or something where it's just pulling the
user identity and then the group
membership. As opposed to the
full configuration, it would be all of
like the SharePoint activity and OneDrive
activity and all of that.
Yeah, thanks. Sorry, Don, did you have
something on this? Yeah, just like this
screen that showed how it's showing here,
here he's mentioning for now identity
only, but you have the option, the
second option it says, I think it
says regular with MIP. Yes, this, this
effect. Our MIP integration and
use cases.
So not for endpoint, but when you guys
do eventually connect, you'll want to
connect with this regular with MIP
because then it will start allowing you
to use that MIP label attribute within
your cloud CASB rules as well. And also
on e-mail if you have a mic encrypted
messages we'll be able to decrypt.
OK. So that's actually a good point
because we have another project that that
that's supposed to do some of these
things. So I think this is where we're
going to choose shadows data. This
approach here design or you shouldn't
matter.
Looking for the out here. This is
just so I understand because there's a
few different integrations here. Is this
DSM sign or is this this is
a DLP IBM side OK and this
is to retrieve the user list from
M365. So like that Ultra,
So the identity only option would be that
and then yeah, the regular with MIP label
would be the full cloud permissions along
with the MIP integration.
OK, I'm a little OK. So and what is
what is doing with bulk here? Is this
from SAS direct or like what is doing the
interaction with our employee 6510?
Yeah, yeah. It's the SASS tool,
so. OK,
I'm I mean this is API
based so the regular with MIP
labels. This will be configured when
you guys are ready to stand
up the entire cloud DLP tool.
So it will include many permissions,
not just the identity permissions. It
will it will include all of like the
SharePoint activity, OneDrive activity. I
don't remember all of them off the top of
my head, but all of the ones that are
necessary for the cloud, the cloud DLP
tool to work and then identity only. The
reason we're selected or you know, we're
talking about this one right now is that
because the cloud. OP, project hasn't
started. You do have an option to
make an API connection that will only
pull the identity. So you can use
the user attributes like group membership
within an item rule. Yelp rule. That's
for like the user catalog. Yes, I've
seen that term a few times. So.
I'll hit one second on that.
And, and, and you guys, I think Howard
had it, but, um, Chad, did you look
at the yeah, this is the, the guide.
This should have all of the permissions
in there. Um, not I don't think the
identity only option has the specified
permissions in here, but the full Casby.
Permissions that are required will, you
know, will be outlined here. Yeah. The
thing that I can see given a strong
here is actually the cache information. I
know we had this issue with another
product, right and it was too invasive
and we got shut down completely. So I
think we're going to take this back and
kind of. Determining what what's required
for each of the options and then make
those decision. Most likely the pattern
less resistant. And if we have to come
back and and do an IP a little time,
that would be a little bit easier because
it's just some modification work we
already have rather getting shut down
from the get go. OK, I'm looking at a
different doc online. About user catalog
overview for Data Security Workbench, it
looks different from what you're reading
here. I don't know, I've never seen this
one before. If you want, yeah, this is
this is the, this is the guide for
the entire cloud DLP. You're probably
just looking at like a document for like
within the console. And just on the the
user catalog, yeah, yeah, that I think
that document is just like going over
what it is. This is more of like how
to get it connected, OK. OK, I'll check
this out with your chat so you can have
it. To do
that right now, OK, so I believe it
is for identity only and we'd have to
verify, but I believe it's user read all,
group read all, group member read all,
and then direct directory read all. I
believe it's just those four. What does
it mean that we haven't started the cloud
DLP projects?Like terminology on the
proof point side versus TV side, like is
this still on the TV side bundles as
our DLP component or is this something
that you guys bought like the entire kind
of DLP suite, right? So there's endpoint
ITM, there's e-mail DLP, and then there's
cloud DLP, so the cloud. Hope you guys
have purchased, but we haven't yeah, we
haven't begun that like set up of that
tool. I mean we can do it concurrently. I
don't know if there's like a roadblock. I
think Howard had just mentioned that they
they need to review like the entire
permissions that are being requested
before they move forward. But yeah, that
is a separate tool it's. You might hear
it as called called as Casby or Claudio.
We kind of use them interchangeably.
Yeah. How are the reason I ask that is
because if that's going to be like a
separate app code, then that changes a
lot of things, right. So, so again, it's
kind of like testing whether we're even
going to turn it on and win, right.
Right. Exactly. That's exactly what it
is. It's going to be a different mode.
We don't have a cascade solution to
there, right. So we decided to discover
that app from this project and but we're
going to revisit this next year. So it
will include it for our FY25 planks. OK.
So it's on the radar. OK, got it.
Talk like on like a fruit point platform
level like when we say we've got this
ideal, people don't call it Cosby because
it enables our cloud integration with
your cloud apps. So for example, by
giving example of being able to extract
the MIP label for e-mail. That's that's
one use case we talked about user catalog
you have DSM as part of the. Project so
I think of like data access governance if
DSP needs to take a remediation action
it's and and Office 365 it's going to
leverage cloud DLP so that that's that's
why it's broken out like that so you
may need it depending on your use case
like so let me give this product specific
thing that's. This case specific, we have
to think of it as product specifically
like we like, I have to by design, right?
Like I, I get your point like, but, but I
think that you described it well. Like
ESPN is doing the scanning to figure out
what's going on. But if you need to take
remediation actions, you got, you got to
have that, that piece in place. So I
think that's fair, right.
Yep. OK, well, perfect. And and if if
you feel like things could change based
on approach just like this one, cuz we
can pivot, we have as high risk. And
now just pointed out, you have the bundle
of products. We've been focused on rules
and policies for D excuse me for the
end point primarily. IBM and some and
then pieces of elsewhere, but we hadn't
really drilled down on the well. I'll
call it the cloud solution yet.
How Howard, for what you need, do you
like what do you need right now? Like is
it just the identities or would you want
to have the MIP or MIP is sort of like
the thing to look at next year or like
when you know what I mean? Like what's
the bare minimum? I mean, yeah, I can't
because I know what's happening with our
team on the on the. With other projects,
right, I think it would be beneficial to
actually have a mic integration,
especially because these tied up with the
e-mail component and and that's what
we're trying to take files going through
emails with you know, preview controls,
right It seems that if we don't have that
in place, we won't be able to read the
emails so. You have to make a decision
like do we want to do it now or do
we align with the timelines from the
other project and then have that
integrated here? But that's for me. Let
me talk to it and get running the project
and see if that's something that we want
to do. If you ask me, just because
there's less resist them by going with
the. With the regular, you know, the what
you call it the the my gosh, the
identity only this will be less resistant
because we're just pulling the Pacific
Time. I will go with this, but I
need to think about the next thing like
how this contact me on from the other
probably perspective and you know, people
complaining about. You know, protecting
flaws like we have an alley coming our
way because people this question is some
of this deal, the controls, but. And
there's enough. It makes sense. Yeah.
Thank you. Yeah. We'll see. We'll see how
it goes. I'll let you know. Probably let
it today unless done. Do you have the
answer for that?Sorry,
say that again Howard, I was just
distracted based on what you guys are
doing with other project. Do
you guys think that we should be
integrating with the? Yeah, that's why I
mentioned with that. I mean, I, I would,
I would think that, but, um. I,
I, I do agree that you should, we should
have a wider internal conversation to
sync up and make sure on the same page,
right? And, and I also get your, your
way, like just to get the progress going.
Maybe the identity only is easiest now,
but you're eventually going to have to
need this. So is it better now?
But maybe the internal sync up can can
help with that before we decide now.
Yeah, I agree, agree. So let's take that
internally and we'll figure it out. We'll
let you know if it's not, it's going to
be early next week. Chat, we'll try to
get that out of the way because we do
need to get these integrated ASAP, right?
Yeah, Yeah, yeah. So I'm, I'm apologizing
for creating a little bit of from last
week on the on the DP e-mail side. The
only thing that we have to do based on
the conversation that we had last week is
that we have to go into that
configuration and we have to do an import
of this. So and that's where we put our.
Information that's correct, right? OK,
perfect. Now on the DPM
side, there is this linkage
from the app catalog where
we can actually click on
the ESPN and that takes
us there. So do we
still need to do anything?
On the DSM side to to to
augment the data that would call in,
because I saw that there's a
configuration where you pull the e-mail
addresses and stuff to actually kind of
map some of the findings. Does this
integration that we do with the DSP
platform helps?With the SPM integration
or remove that that need or do we have
to do a separate integration and the
integration for the SPM to to pull eighty
groups or the United States is singing
behind the curtains?
Now do you want to take that one? I'm I'm
not sure on the DSM sound. Does it still
use that same user catalog that we do?
The road map, I think we're going to
have a call with the PM for that.
It's, uh, window become available. We'll
understand today, just separate app to do
the user catalog import on and normalize
or discount. We always
need to come to normalize, say ohh, I
still do integration. So let let me just
give me a second if you don't mind. I'll
need to probably defer that handle on
this. I don't know if we'll be able to
cover that too. So yeah, previously he
previously told us that it's.
Aside Carter or an Azure site that gets
stood up to interact with a round trip,
I can't remember. Yeah, yeah, that's what
he mentioned. I was hoping that this
integration here would remove the need
for setting up that sidecar. Yeah, yeah,
that's the direction timeline we'll we'll
have a call with. Yeah. And we can
discuss that. Hopefully it's more closer
than not. OK, that would be great. But we
still have to go and do something for the
lower environment. That's OK. Perfect.
All right. So that is sort of the way.
So this gives me ammunition to go on and
try to get these, these these two things
at least out of the way. Next week,
a fool, I guess. What when did you
guys think we can get the information for
the for the new API? I mean, I,
I really, I really talked to the
developers and looking to have a call
with somebody from professional services
that can actually walk us through the new
API. And especially around the end points
that that we will need to utilize to
go and pull the data that is required
for our data retention app. Is that
something that?Apologize, I
want to make sure I'm be specific.
Are you talking about pulling up the
activities from the platform or the
endpoint pushing? Yeah. It's
going to be both, right? Like it's based
on that conversation that we had earlier
this week where you guys proposed a new,
a new approach so we can actually get all
the data and evidence that we need,
right. So we would like to take how the
endpoints will actually connect like
programmatically, what do we need to do
on our side. Like how we can
actually pull that data via the API
from all the different endpoints so we
can actually ingest that now? Yeah, I
mean, maybe on this talk, Harris, we
could talk about external configuring
external storage on the RAM level for
the endpoints to push to there could
be configured. Azure Storage, As for the
data delivery API, it's part of dev
tools. It's just another endpoint. So we
can have a call about it, but it's
not not unlike what you've already been
doing with the Activity API. It's just,
you know, you would, you would, you would
go in, you create the user, you create
the OAT groats. And then you'd use it. So
yeah, I'm just trying to say sometimes
because like I mentioned, they called
again, we don't know what we're looking
for. And my understanding this is a new
API. So if we can get some guidance over
the call somebody that that is familiar
with it and say, OK, this is this is what
you're trying to do, this is where how to
tackle it, right? This is what you get.
What you gotta push to send to get
whatever you need just because remember
the first use cases that we had with the
API, we went over like a probably a
couple of weeks to try to figure it out,
like and trying to say it was a couple
of weeks, yeah, here's the one that you
want. We'll probably schedule with the
resource. To talk about the day delivery
API, OK, what do you recommend? Well,
sorry, did you say that you're going to
schedule a time? Do you want to pull
in like?
We started to talk about the data
delivery API and we could talk about
during our next session or Steve is
available. Yeah, I could use these
available and we'll try to get it on the
books as soon as we can. OK, so here's
the deal with that. See if we can get
like my goat into Jordan.
We're talking about the migration script
from one point to point B or something.
No, no, no, there's in the new API, Tim.
Ohh. OK, so we got to set up a call
with Mike to present this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I was doing
something that we just need a meeting. Is
it with customer or internal for us? Just
give me a heads up, Harris, and I'll make
sure it gets done. Yeah, I'll send you a
message tone. All right, Got it. Thank
you. OK,
perfect. Yeah. And I would like to be
more like a, you know, the emotions that
we all like a working session. Like if we
can combine both that would be great,
right. But just because I will have the
developers available for that goal,
right. So you know those guys actually
have 30 mostly that so.
And no, but I believe you're working on
the on the Visio diagram, right or
something someone on our team is and will
follow up with that individual and and
when we can provide it. Yeah, how would
I should have an update to you shortly
on when that Visio diagram or I'll call
it the. Diagram, the program designed for
the API will be complete. I think it's
just putting the finishing touches on it
before we make it fit for purpose. I
should have an update on that imminently
and provide it to you because I'm aware
you know how important and critical it is
for you to have that information. OK,
perfect. Thank you. Uh, Harris
already told me about this or he's
going to be running the update next
week. Sorry. OK,
yeah, the script, Yeah, yeah, got
it. All right. The next week.
So my apologies, Sir. I cannot fix it.
No, I didn't take your time. You're up
at 2:30 in the morning, Howard. So just
we're here. We we've got 30. We've got
another 30 minutes since we have time.
Yeah, I actually wanted to talk about
that as well because I found some, I
don't know, something. That I'll bring it
up in a second, guys. Another thing that
we've come across yesterday is that when
we were trying to map environments and
trying to see why certain things were not
working, we realized that. When we log
into the production instance, it is
called TD Bank Group.
TD Bank Group Yeah, this is the
one. Uh, give me one SEC. Let's
see if we can actually log in
just to center have ordered that Why?
Sorry, I'm just going to be a second. I
just want to show you what we counted
there.
I mean, there's nothing critical. It's
just like we're trying to understand why
this is there.
Why do we see it at all?
Uh, so when we actually logging
yesterday, we thought this was a weird,
you know, POC instance. We'd never
thought it was going to be production of
the bank. We start sniffing around after
effect to you guys, right? We came across
with activity.
In this platform. And
after doing a lot of filtering,
we realized that this was, um,
isolation activity. That's correct, yes.
You guys know that small license
for browser isolation. Yeah. And it's
going to be recording this console.
Yeah. OK, so let me ask
you this. Yeah, I went into users
and I went to administration. I don't see
it. Well, I see people here.
Right. I was saying that all this sorry,
no users, No, this is not what I want
to read. My apologies, Sir. Those are
isolated. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it.
The the isolation app. OK, so they don't
want trying to get is they don't have
access to what we're going to be setting
up, right, Because I didn't see them
here. And we did try actually clicking
on isolation and that basically refused
our access. I'm guessing that's because
this is just getting to those guys. We
just wanted to clarify that what? That's
what he says. He refuses your access. So
you yeah, he just goes nowhere. And he
said we need to have unauthorized. Sleep
lock achieve block page. OK, OK, we could
stand for that. But yeah, yeah, it's part
of the product. I think. I don't know if
the how productive this use case. I think
you have like some privilege or maybe a
Swift use or something that in order to
use the browser, they need to only be
able to use it through browser isolation.
Right. Yeah, um.
There are e-mail use cases for isolation.
We embed isolation into e-mail security.
We embedded as a reverse proxy for
cloud DLP. But but yeah, you should
expect to see this in production. So
as long as you have the license,
I mean, we could definitely if.
If you want to remove this activity for
a specific type of user, we can create
a custom access policy to exclude
isolation. Yeah, that's probably what
we're going to do because it just for
somebody that is not familiar and
especially when we hand over these
operations, right, you're going to come
into activities. You understand? Yeah.
Web browser theory, What is this? And
it's just going to create additional work
that we don't want. We probably just set
it up to the role so we don't see
that kind of stuff, right? Yeah, but
that's fine. That's OK. We were just.
Wondering about that another and this
kind of is a good Segway for another
issue that we had so.
The data security posture management, so
we got this link and this is our
production instance, right? So if I click
on this, right, it does take me to
the SPM, I can see everything that we
do, right?And you
know, I could see my scans, it's
going to go figurations and everything,
right? The question that I have, what
are the restriction of the mutation like
is there anything that I need to
go back to the other portal and
do that is not available from here?
I'm not sure how or when you
say switch team at the top right.
You got the three tenants. No, it's
just one. It's the wrong tenant. Oh,
there you go. Yes. Yeah. This. This.
Ohh. Wow. Yeah, this is abundant.
I could I could cancel my e-mail.
But actually, actually, well, yeah, we
gotta fix this too. OK, Yeah.
That's good, Yeah. It's it's good that
you catch that didn't actually pay
attention to that little drop that. No,
but that isn't it isn't about that hard.
It's just good that we can rectify this
and you can move forward, that's all.
Yeah, yeah, but we have to get that at
TD Bank Group. It's like, so it's linked
to the wrong. This
camp DSP tenant um.
I I'm gonna have to defer to her
go off on some of that. And if
the call that we're going to set up
with product. So I think Tim is going
to arrange a call with Nancy to talk
about like the road map, but also talk
about what's coming with the Kubernetes
scanner so. And can we defer that
to that call? Yeah. Yeah, I
could. But um, but this to the challenge
that we're facing right now and and this
is where we start looking into the
mapping and all these things, right?
When we log into.
We logged into app the normalized IO with
our current e-mail addresses, right, like
a production e-mail accounts, right. We
see that allocation where we actually see
scanners, we see everything we can
perform the scans and then we start
looking through the data and realize that
even though we went and we see.
All detectors where we thought things
were, there were no actually those
configurations were not being honored by
the Deadspin solution. And then we
started looking around and say, well this
seems to be mapping to the run
detectors. So what what we have right
now is a situation where our ESPN.
Solution. Doesn't have
the right configuration in place, so if
I go to add the normalizer IO,
it should be. Supposed to
be mapping everything from here, but we
didn't do the work here because we didn't
know about this. So it's building our
configuration. Everything that we did was
on the dev side, so that's the reason why
nothing showing there. So we were trying
to figure it out how we can get all
this mapped properly so we can get higher
risk. Especially more of the detectors,
right? And then get all this synchronized
across the board so we can actually run
this scan. That's how we get into this
problem, right? And how we realized this.
Now we can't believe this impact because
apparently there's no path payment, but
you mentioned that there's a payment,
there's no relief map. DSM 10, yeah.
So we gotta fix this. So yeah, kind of
like the same e-mail this regard to like
the issue that we're looking at.
I, I hope to get that resolved shortly.
So and then I think in terms of like
being able to have detectors for the
right tenant, I think that that would be
resolved once that's fixed.
Right. Yeah. But yeah, we just wanted to
bring this up, right, like because this
is just affecting our testing like what I
was telling the guys, unfortunately now
we're going to have to create all these
pictures from earlier on this stuff for
us. But we'll wait probably a couple of
days more Monday, Tuesday and see if that
gets. Right now, but if it's internal
like you feel free just to make sure I
have understand it correctly. I just
reached out to have up to take a look
to maybe aligned on tenant and the
mapping. I think that's a first pass,
right? Or is there someone else I got to
make sure I reach out to you? Who would
you advise?Yeah, I think we'll
have to take that offline. Yeah. But OK,
that's that's obviously something that's
not that is unresolved. OK, All right,
all right, I got it. I'll leave it alone
for now, but I have a meeting coming up
in 30, hopefully get it solved in.
OK, perfect. So I'm going to talk
about the DSP and partitioning because
I'll leave that for UMM.
Role mapping and your restrictions so the
do do we have anyone from the DSM
side mall? Are you here I can't remember
what was this about This was the
segregation of duty. Remember the like if
we get governance to to go in and
look at explorations or even get access
to the. Say the DPC cordo,
are they going to be like can
we do granular RBAC stuff where we
cannot let them see the ITM related
stuff as a versus just relying on
tagging? Oh yeah, yeah, I remember now.
Yeah. So I think this was in
your play. Like I remembered you taking
this back at some point indicating that
they were going to test the the access
and then provide us with the document on
or run book to actually be able to
implement these on our site, restricting
people's view only to IPM based on their
role. I don't know if you
send that document or you still working
on that.
And if you're taking your problem, mute.
Or not talking. Yeah, sorry, no, I was on
mute. Yeah. So it is,
it is going to be based on the tagging,
right. So I think we talked about can,
can you open that admin page. So I
remember when we initially talked about
it, you weren't seeing any tags there.
But when I signed into your tenant, I was
actually seeing the tags when I tried to
create a custom access policy. So
yeah, if you go here to access
policies on the left and then just
do new custom access policy.
And you could just call this what have
you guys created the tax for four ITM or
for DLP?That I feel
and this deal we talk as well right? OK,
alright, that's fine. Um, let let me go
to there because that's where we have the
tags right now. Give me a second.
He's looking for that. Just wondering,
um, does this So basically I can't
remember recall off hand. Like can you
put tags on data classes as well
or?No, you
cannot. So the data classes are
pretty much a.
Like you either have it open to the
whole team or you have closed, right. Is
that the same for like conditions,
detectors, smart ID's, all of those
things? Yeah, yeah, yeah. There's with
conditions, actually. Conditions you
might be able to put tags. Yeah, I
think you could put tag like conditions.
What are definitions here? Howard on at
the bottom and then go to conditions.
Uh, yeah. So yeah, you can tag these. Um,
let me check. I don't think you can do
them on the data classes or smart ID's. I
haven't checked that. Let me just take a
quick look. So.
Ohh. See.
But if you go, go up to access
policies there.
And you could just create a new access
policy and you could just do like ITM.
Users, yeah, OK, So Don, I'm looking
at the data classes and detectors right
now. You can't tag those unfortunately,
right? So yeah, they would still be
able to see.
And they swing. That's also true for
explorations. You can't like expert, if
you have access to the exploration page,
you see everything that's there. Well,
you can. You can lock certain
explorations so only you can view them.
But if you're referring to the metadata,
like just the activity that's generated,
that's not triggering the rule. I think
you should be able to still, um, you
should be able to still restrict that
based on the signal type. So I'm going to
show you here on the next page.
So choose the Yeah, select template type,
choose the first one, Activity
exploration, and then yes, select OK
here. Put Yeah do field No, sorry,
do the field here.
And um, first do the tags so you
can just type in tag or rule tag.
Yeah, it'll be under alert there.
Rule tags and then select value. So
you should see them in here now.
Yeah, so if you search ITM.
OK, so select this. So this
should cover the alerts. And now
for the metadata, if you click
add row and then yeah, and
then select field right above there.
And then do just type in signal typehere.
Yep. So this portion should cover
the metadata field. So just do
ITM here.
And then that system is just like
the system generated like, uh, platform
audit activities. So yeah, I mean this
when you assign it to a user,
this should only allow them to see
these activity that. You
know alerts that map to this item
tag and then the metadata that's mapped
to the ITM signal type. OK, so
if I applied this to you more.
Um, it's anybody else
working on ITM Evan
maybe?But
doesn't this restrict access to?
The policies and the
rules are just.
So once we are granted access this
way, it removes our access to the
policies, right? No, this is just, this
is just a single access policy. So
if you go up to users here
now it's not it's not just this
specific one, right? So we still have
the. You could still add
like the like the configuration add Yeah.
So go to mom or something here.
Yeah. So what you would do is
yeah, click on this and then, um.
It click click on this so you can remove.
You might not want to remove it now, but
at some point you should be able to see.
Yeah, you should be able to assign all of
these in addition to that new one that we
created. Yeah. So
whatever other access you want them to
have, but what we created there, that
should just restrict the access on the
workbench page. So they should only be
able to see alerts that have the ITM tag
and then the metadata that's captured by
the ITM signal type. Everything else on
the console you guys can determine like
what level of access. Want to give you
some those like granular access policies.
So yeah, that's just one access policy,
right? You can, you can still assign
more. OK.
And it's similar to this. And you, you
play around with it and that's. Yeah,
sure. Uh-huh. Ohh. Thanks. When you're
testing it, though, no, yeah. We're going
to need to remove that full admin, right?
Because yeah, I'll probably sign in and
then test it and see, And then you
can. OK. Thank you.
OK. Yeah. I'll see if there's any
other way for the detectors, but I'm
looking right now there.
I don't think there's a way. It's either
you give them access to that entire
detectors page, or you just restrict
access altogether. Same thing
with data classes, smart ID's, all of
that.
Sounds good, Good. All right. Just
because we have only 12 more minutes and
I'd like to open it up to actually to
the floor at the rest of the Teams chat.
I start with you. You know me. Do you
have any question for Proofpoint?
No, no, nothing, nothing urgent. I think
we're kicking out. Alright. Perfect.
Alright, So engineering, you guys have
any questions for Proofpoint, any issue
that you're running into or something
that you guys would like clarification?
No, no, it just sounds like the. I'm
glad the the tenant mapping thing is
going to be. Like a
priority because I think once that starts
going and we can see the red detectors,
if I feel like that will that will
be a big. Two
step forward, yeah, definitely,
definitely because like it will start
making sense of where we actually
flagging right now versus where this
expectations are.
Following this call, remember, just send
me just send me a quick e-mail with like
you know where the detectors and data
classes exist today, which tenant and
then where you want them moved to Yeah,
we'll do that we'll do that Let me just.
Complications I want to follow
up.
Can you ask them your name? OK.
Yeah. OK. Alright, great. Do you think I
saw you doing thumbs up? Do you have
a question? No, all good here. Thanks.
We'll probably just talk about the the
new API that you're talking about. I
wasn't, I wasn't aware of that, but maybe
there's some sort of documentation to get
at. Before our call. That would be great.
Yeah. And how I know
how groups are on the call I have
you guys. Do you
have anything going happening with the
snippet storage?That that's supposed
to be covered under that same API. Umm,
right now we do have a sniper storage on
the PM side. What is it set up in
production, right. And we're able to see
the snippets. I think we still need to
have another Internet conversation on how
this is going to work in the long term.
But yeah. OK, I can expand on it. So how
it's going to work in the long term is
DSM is going to use the same snippets
knowledge as the rest of the data
security platform. So there will be no
difference in how snippets are handled.
I, I'm on an impression it's going to
come sometime in, in this, this calendar
quarter. But again, I'm going to, we're
going to have another call with the PM
for data security platform and we'll add
that to the agenda. OK, perfect. This
might be a silly question, but obviously
snippet means a subset of a big picture
is what I'm assuming so. Can can
you reiterate what this snippet actually
contains?Per per incident or
event or or whatever.
Um, a snippet would be like for us
to be the aunt, the unmasked text that
matched the policy. So if you see like
an endpoint DLP, it will show like all
the smart ID matches that we were
detecting with them. So it would be
specifically that are you looking to have?
There is also include like text
before and after they no. So
just verifying that this snippet is
just a violation preview. That's right.
OK, OK.
And and like one other thing I'd point
out to Howard is that the snippets are
masked. Like if you when we start doing
the the JSON web hook alert, they're
masked and and then there's the Activity
API where you can unmask the snippet.
OK. So, so like what most of
my customers do is they unmask based
on an investigation versus let's say on
mass everything.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Makes sense. Uh, we probably need to
figure it out on our once we start
developing our application, if we want to
basically create a set of functionality
within it that we just click a button
that says decrypt and it shows them that
those details, right? And maybe we can do
that based on role based. Control as
well, do you think the same way we do it
with the with the with the item stuff,
right. But what we'll figure it out,
we'll ask for help. Sorry. Go ahead,
Chad. Yeah, question on that and I'm
actually going to look back. I remembered
the snippets question and thank you for
raising it, but just to understand, so
that means there's an API to retrieve
encrypted. Methods that we could store
locally and then when we would need to
decrypt them you call another API to and
pass it back for the decryption. Is that
my understanding it right? No, So the
snippets are recorded in the platform
because that why we does it there is
because we have attribute role based
access control so that allows us to
unmask. And ask the snippets. We also
have the option to write all snippets to
external storage, right?Also
in the court, we also have as
part of the dev tools we have
at the activity API where if you
want to, if you're pulling, let's say
the activities or taking the, the the
one click alert we have the snippets
are going to be are going to
be mass. And then we have an
API where you can request that activity,
the snippets within that activity to be
unmasked.
So using the activity API you can't. But
I'm confused about what you're pulling
them. If you're pulling a mask snippet or
yeah, the snippets and the JSON alert are
going to be mass. If you need to
unmask it then you would call the
activity API. There's like this snippet.
And points that you would call to unmask
the snippet.
OK, with some sort of reference ID
to whichever that exactly OK, OK.
OK, that's, that's interesting.
Yeah. OK. That's
fine. That's fine for now. I think
there's stuff to be explored there still,
but that's that's good. Thank you.
Perfect. Thank you. I had a couple of
things going on, but I'll save it for the
next session. They're not important right
now. So Tim, I think you have some
updates for us or you have some comments
that you wanted to bring up.
Unit, Raleigh.
Howard, we were you asking me or? Yeah,
Yeah. You mentioned when you joined that
you had a couple of updates for us. I
think we covered all of them. It was more
I wanted to make sure that the, you know,
the ticket that was escalated yesterday,
It's it sounds like to me. I still need
some work to do behind the scenes. I just
got to kind of work through internally
how that's going to play out, so give me
time on that. If it looks like a
configuration error, at least that's my.
So stay tuned for that. You
got the you haven't collected what
was around 85 the dying diagram
for API, which we have. I
just I I know some people
just looking at it one more
time before we. You know we sent
out, you know, fit for purpose. You know,
again, we've met. And
he talked about it, but let
me follow up with yeah, man
for that.
Sorry, it's it's Mayo team is coming
out. Yeah, he's cutting out.
OK, ohh, that's alright. I just want to
make sure I do.
Yeah, we're we're gonna hear what you're
saying. I'm sorry. DJ's using the theater
on him. Yeah, I think he I think
he got disconnected, but OK, we'll we'll
let him know if he has any updates.
I'll just shoot you an e-mail. Yeah,
yeah. Just one last thing before No. Yes,
yes, maybe I'll. Have that to you in
about an hour that that I was just
waiting for someone to review it. That's
all. Sounds good. It doesn't have to be
in an hour like at the end of the day or
the Monday that that works too right to
touch me. The bikes, yeah. My,
my thinking on that was if you have some
homework you need to do, I'd like you to
have it in your hands the way I know you
work anyway, but I'd like you to have it
for at least ahead of Monday. How's that?
All right. Sounds good. Sounds good.
Thank you. Appreciate it. Yeah, I'll
probably look at it at it over the
weekend. Just one
more thing guys, were you planning to
go? You probably know this, uh, we,
we planning a pilot groups to be
deployed next month, probably towards the
end of August and most likely the
next, the next few sessions leading to
their deployment will be. A little bit
more intensive, like a handsome trying to
work few things, you know, trying to make
sure that the policies are working as
expected. The reason why we haven't
started that yet is because we still
don't have the full AD integration. So we
can't really pull the groups and have all
our policies the way we want them. But
once we have that integration in place,
which I'm hoping it's going to be next
week. Um, then we'll have more intense
sessions where we're actually going to go
and specific details, making sure the
policies are marked, a flag is completed
and keep moving forward so we can
actually meet our goal next month. So.
Just letting you know, things are going
to be changing a little bit more on our
side. It's going to be more like a
working session type of thing. OK, Yeah.
Thanks for the heads up.
All right, that's not powered. Enjoy your
weekend. Hopefully you sign off at 5:00
today and enjoy your Friday and Saturday
and we'll connect next week. We'll do.
Alright guys. Well, thank you guys again.
Thank you. Bye.